(Sheldon:)By any standard,
Amy is more similar to me
(Sheldon:)than anyone I've ever met.
(Mrs Cooper:)Oh, I'm sorry, Shelly,
I can't see it.
(Sheldon:)Well, whether you see
it or not is irrelevant.
(Sheldon:)I can't see subatomic particles,
(Sheldon:)but nevertheless, they're there.
(Amy:)Excellent point.
(Sheldon:)A physics point.
Touché.
(Mrs Cooper:)Well, putting aside the pig Latin,
(Mrs Cooper:)it's a good thing that
(Mrs Cooper:)you two decided to
end the relationship
(Mrs Cooper:)so I didn't have to end it for you.
(Sheldon:)Amy, after consideration,
(Sheldon:)I believe we may have acted rashly.
(Sheldon:)I propose we resume
our relationship
(Sheldon:)and attempt to resolve
our differences.
(Amy:)I'll agree to that only
if you'll stipulate
(Amy:)that 80% of our difficulties
were caused by you.
I'll go as high as 40. Sixty-five.
(Sheldon:)Done.
(Sheldon:)You understand that moving forward,
(Sheldon:)we deal with the fact that my
mother does not approve of you?
(Amy:)I do. I find being cast
(Amy:)in the role of bad
girl oddly titillating.
(Sheldon:)Would you like to see my cats?